Welcome to the night, the cars laid out for show Star shine is so bright, watch the
secrets unfold
we are came
necessary to do. I finally got my natural color going. It looks pretty good. Am I cuter than
VeganPatriot? That's all I want to know. No? Let me know. VeganPatriot, I'm coming for your
crap. I think I'm cuter than her. What do you think? He's scared of me now, but he's
I mean, like, come on good
So
Yeah, this is like, I mean, it's not
My hair would look like this about as an albino and I like took really good care of it
Could have happened, I could have been born without treatment
There's not special effects, you're not into just your television
This is the real deal.
Let's see.
Turn off the green screen.
There we go. Let's go.
Let's begin.
I mean, I think I look
relatively good.
Up to here, everyone's opinion about it.
It is a new look. I know it's a new look can be drastic a little bit, but...
People will work out
Not trying to lose your good attention. I mean, it's like yes, it's a
Amazing way, I mean
So I'd like an old lady though, I mean the kind of white a little bit white I was hoping to be more blonde
but I
Mean I'm not
One's in hand. I just need to know. Am I cuter than Beacon Patriot? Well, I want to know. And I'll leave.
Good answer. Okay. Well, there's one person here. I guess we can premiere some stuff. What time is it?
4.48. Why didn't anybody awake? It should be like 8 o'clock. Eastern time. Almost. Okay. Well,
Okay, well, we'll play video.
I'll play one.
I'll play that one later.
That one's good.
Finish it. Okay
Way ahead of myself guys way ahead of myself, but I need some feedback on my new look I
Have this new shirt to see
It's not supposed to be that feminine. It's supposed to be like I guess like the L from Lord of the Rings or something
Or look like him
I mean, if I was trying to live with a woman, I would have, like, really, more of an effort to shave and put on some nice makeup and stuff.
But still, no matter that, I still think I'm cuter than being a patriot.
You know who we have to ask? Well, we have to ask Mr. Bigpipes, his opinion about it.
His hill have an opinion about it.
I'll probably choose her.
What's wrong with Divis? Why are you making that face?
You don't like it?
What do I look like? Is it like, is there like some kind of like...
Oh yeah, so this is the perfect song to play with, you know, kind of like a kind of like a
a vampire maybe, the undead perhaps? You guys hear me by the way? Let me just...
Well, I'll see.
Almost there. How was everyone's morning, D.B.? Do I know you? I've never seen you before here.
I've never seen you before then you should be seeing this for the first time and then it shouldn't be like that
Should we make your face about it?
I understand
Controversial sometimes. Oh
Good morning, Achilles, Kate. Hi. Do you like my new hairstyle? I think it looks better. I needed a change in my look and
I think this works for me
But when I it looks like some kind of like albino kind of vampire what again from Norway or something
Okay, we'll have a song song about I'm not a vampire. Okay, everyone's been trying to claim their vampire lately
I'm not a vampire. I really am not
but this is
The blonde is a choice. It is a choice. I mean, I mean, it's kind of white
But like I said a better look at the vegan Patriot as long as I'm better as a computer the vegan Patriot
I'll be okay with the you know wearing this full-time
But if not, then I was probably like, you know
We're up something to do on Halloween with it, but I want it I want this to work so badly
It's gonna stay this nice for like a day, and then it's gonna
Either catch on fire or like get really dirty. I mean, you know me
Well, I get the dirty but anyway, okay. Okay. Well, let's do this
awesome very happy with that very happy thank you we love the look thank you grim reaper yeah i'm
i mean i don't know people are like i'm dead like everyone wants to be a vampire i don't want to
be a vampire i want to be like maybe just more swedish maybe just want to give me i am like
part swedish and so i just want to like really like that myself i was actually bored with this color
Yeah, of course, I can't grow it like this, and of course, I can't bleach it like this, so...
Thank you. I think it looks okay.
Like I said,
cuter than being a patriot.
But I need like a, probably a female to help me like figure stuff out, though.
I'm kind of a disaster when I'm much unsupervised.
That's a terrible joke. Okay, what I have is the E of vampires. Here's how I prove I'm not a vampire
Oh, excuse me. I'm drinking this garlic cookies
Okay
That's proof enough
Even though there's no garlic in this nor cookies
there is weed and
I feel like I should be wearing like a really cute outfit though and like maybe have this really cool shirt like you said my shirt
Like vaporwave kind of style I was gonna be Vita for Halloween
But they were out of the prosthetic nose and the afro wigs. I just won't look long
Plus, oh my god, I never hear the end of that use me for Halloween
What about with Mesa for Halloween then she'd be mad. He wouldn't even like that
Changed the name to something even didn't sound like the fair name
Thank you, Murray. Thank you
It is like a who's it reminds me of like, um
There's a show called hey
Everybody yeah, there's a show called it was like about the
It's called race
WRA I THS rates and I kind of like the rate
You see I got find the guy's picture
He's like blonde and like really pale
kind of like me, but I
Have a kind of a nicer
Intone even though I'm not really in the Sun. I should be like a lot wider
The look natural
I mean, I'm no Suzanne Summers, but
It's really sad if I take off the wig I'm just wearing a hair net
So I look like I've been working at a school cafeteria or something
under this, but
Check out the hair net
Okay, so I was just gonna I don't know everyone got bored already if though
I'm just waiting to like have some time till McDonald's opens and it's open
I'll still, um, play something else.
Be.
Moonlight dripping from her blade
Whispers hex the silver rail
Love dies laughing in her lips
He's trembling in the undertow
Begging shadows not to show
But spell hums love and fire
Venus with a blade of spine
Every man on earth, every flame of friend
And she li-
Should I do a pole? Let's do it.
Um, let's see. I can't, you can't, I need to go, all right, show. Okay, there it is.
Okay, and then I can do a pole.
No, I'm gonna do it. Create a,
I'm gonna do a damn pole. Oh, probably a digger.
I found it, okay.
cuter. Psyche. Vegan. Patriot.
You guys can just go ahead and go to that bowl. See how it go. Everyone wants to...
I think I'm at 0%, I don't know.
Oh, being a Patriot, 100%.
Oh my gosh.
I don't, I really don't believe that.
Uh-oh, am I frozen?
Hello?
Come on.
Oh, I clocked it.
Yeah, being a Patriot, no, I'm not.
First of all, my pace is better than hers.
Second of all
Well, the week is better than her real hair
The cats are cuter than her animal. I mean it's like she's not a bad person
but
I think I wear it better, but how's the pole going or is it full of a hundred percent?
In someone um three votes a hundred percent everyone's voted against me you guys are all a bunch of traitors
Like you mean even if you didn't think that I was oh
Got one person looking even if you didn't think that I was you would just maybe like you know
You know me, you know, you guys know being patriots
Okay, well at 33% we'll take it I mean
Imagine, but you have to imagine me kind of like, you know, just, you know, on my stomach
bent over.
So you wouldn't even see my face, you'd just see the hair, so it would just be like this.
Like that.
And so you wouldn't even have to see my face.
It just began like, it began like how about like, you know, I look like that, like very
That I could finally win a beauty contest goes and finally got my look I
Can see through it actually it's pretty good and
It's like it's like it's like having a curtain on your face
And how to really how do women handle like this hair going in their face all the time?
Can I get advice, please? I don't understand how you can't live
Like this I can't fix it. I mean it's like here I can fix it
But it's like it's now it's all like a spider web in my face
But how do you deal with this?
It's all oh
My god, I would get so I just cut off all my hair and the winter women cut off their bangs. I mean I
Hate you know, you know, I don't want to kind of leave you know a little bit of scene but like
You ever give oral sex and then you get like a little hair and so can you throw it you would never happen?
It's only happening to me
I'm sorry doesn't it feels like it feels like I have a bigger hair on my face
Well
Gosh guys
It's quite a day.
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being backfired behind head
Mods praying Lord, not again
Welcome to the Paniverse baby hold your ground
Where the chaos hums like a feedback sound
We don't know who's sane, who's banned or blessed
But the vibes unholy and always possess
Scotty causing from the bone
Brags he just dropped a cosmic load
Alex and his mic
live in HD authors they're just smiling sweet y'all need Jesus or at least some sleep
and it's all so true. Ghost is connected, Canada drive timed out, Randall's still typing,
wait to be the just ban me. Laughter static at me, I'll end stream noise.
my show. Michael's ghost comes in and gives me a like. I'm better than DP. Thank you so much.
How did the poll go? I'm used to how the poll's going. Well, I'll be a patriot at 72%,
about 28%. So that's not looking very good for me, especially since it's like my chat home
advantage, you know? And so it should be like, you know, it should have like, you know, at least
Even if it wasn't like true just to make me feel good and not like you know make me sad
And now I feel sad and I
Feel stupid enough. I'm sitting here in a way
Looking worse than being Patriot
That's it. That's not a good state of event. It's actually like really depressing thought actually to me
If anything
I'm not probably not better than anybody but I might be better than vegan
Patriot but I guess I'm not and it's a hard pill to swallow um oh guys but you
know what she is better than me because you know what no one would pay me a
hundred dollars plus a like a $50 cake for me to get in a bikini and sit on the
And they paid her to do that
Can you guys do that guys? I will I will like well, it won't be if you do okay
I'll just get it. I'll get like a cheap cake and I'll I'll like in this video and
you know
You want to throw me a couple hundred bucks?
You know
I can never be worse than that. I'm just kidding. Oh my god
Think but I think elbow ones did offer me like a hundred dollars to shave off my eyebrows. I refused because
Look imagine how weird I would look with that eyebrow. Here's some people without eyebrows. It looks like
You love talking things for a while. I love it, too. If you knew I would like find like the most perfect way
I was like, I didn't have to, I didn't have to go blonde.
Actually, when I first did drag, I did,
I stole my mom's Elvira wig.
It was kind of like, it was Elvira style,
but it was blonde, it was blonde Elvira wig.
My mom was a blonde Elvira.
She always had to be a little bit,
or has to be a little bit, just a little bit different,
but it's a really cool wig.
And, yeah.
You know what, I wasn't planning anything for Halloween.
I was, you know, I was probably like,
I was like Alfred E. Newman one year which was a really cheap costume
It was just like basically it had a little bit of wax
You could put it like make your teeth that it came out had like a red hair dye and had a little pen
You could freckles on yourself
I was supposed to be Alfred E. Newman, okay, and then what else was I was Freddie and
Then I would check out twisted metal the brows look freaky on that dude for real
That oh one second person just you know
Well, you know
Was it a game
Oh, are you talking about the clown sides?
Are you saying I look like a clown
Look at, look into my...
Remember, how do you keep the hair from, like, see how the hair, like, is all going in my face right there?
How do you keep that from doing that?
Oh shit, now I can reveal my actual hair, hold on. That's not a good sign.
I am wearing a hair net, but I don't think I...
So, this is really annoying. I don't like this part of it, like, where it's like...
Because like now I'm not able to find the part the correct part. Is that it?
It's like too difficult to wear this
Okay
This way they say being a woman with women is like not easy
If it's hair in their face, they have makeup if the carry a bag with all their other like stuff and
It's hard
Like
I'm wigging out today, but it's like I think it's the net
But it's kind of like I'm almost as like almost like an old lady
Yeah, see my white wig nice. I mean I can see it in the chat, but
Is this supposed to be a joke against me? Like I am like a literal wig you're trying to say
Huh, I think I keep comment down right now
I'll put this one up. I like this one. Perfect.
That's what I want to have up. I saw the comment. I saw your comment.
Spirit of Hope. Thank you so much. Are you a man or a woman? I can't tell.
I'm sorry. Not like in that thing. You're like,
and gender, I'm saying this can't tell from the picture. It's kind of small.
There's kind of like a man with like a very nice wave to his hair. Like an elderly man.
I don't know.
No, if you're spiritual you understand age is all
Relative
Maybe we could be sisters. I don't know. Do I look old though? I do have the father I like the father's psyche video
It's like I can it's like a but they made me very old in that like I look very old in that here right here
What's that
Okay, so does anybody want to see, I think there's another one I have, I see perhaps.
I think it's this one. Hold on. That's all it looked down on it.
Perfect. Okay.
This is pretty cool. I haven't downloaded it.
Oh, here it is.
Okay, here. Oh.
Watch this.
The baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all, the baddest of them all.
But um, no, I'm not trying to hopefully it's like a it's a kind of like a like an elf
Prince or something like that. Thank you very much. Wyatt Anthony fishpot. I appreciate your support. I've never seen before in the chat
You seem for I'm way cuter
They do plenty of water. Why do I look right up? I
Bet you drink water memory because you live in there like a moon right after all
I just need to train the hair. It takes time or just put back. Oh, yeah
Look at me. They gave me the painting of like Burbank. So I use these on anything
I mean, that's the thing with Teemu is like, yeah, it will make sense to get like the wig
and the wig will be like, okay, but it's like, then there's a problem because like, then they
give you this, like, what is this supposed to do? That would, first of all, these would look really
bad in the wig. Like, it's like, they're like just really off color, like, mustard and off
yellow and brown. I mean, why would you put these in your hair? And then it's like, second of all,
Not even like elastic. I mean, it's like they're the cheapest bands
So they put no money on these and they put all the money in the wig
Which they should do because it's like you're buying the wig. I don't even care about these
I if they didn't have these in the bag, I wouldn't don't even care. I need like maybe
Yeah, I think a clip like that'd be nice. They won't do it like clip. Oh, they didn't have a hair net though
The hair net worked out pretty good
Okay
We'll see if I live.
Actually, so the father of Psyche is interesting
because my uncle was actually like very high
in the Church of England.
He was a University of Cairo professor there.
He did something with Vatican and stuff
and he was a lecturer.
He was really a brilliant person,
but we didn't really know it.
You have beautiful eyes.
Leave it down.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
I have beautiful eyes.
I didn't even smile so I don't look so wrinkled, right?
Thank you there. I was like definitely cute of them being patient right there. Let me see the ball right now
In the 3862. Okay. Well, I still have some time. I'll leave that you leave me. Yeah
There's a funny on TikTok sometimes that like, you know, there's a really hot guy long to talk and I
But like most of them are straight, but then most of them figured out like oh, you know
If you're nice to gay guys, they'll probably give you like, you know roses and which are actually just money
You know, it's like it's just like it's like it's like not very much
I can give 100 100 roses and that's what a dollar right and speaking to their press a hundred times and they're like whoa
And it's like a lot of people are just like you do it. So they're kind of like shocked. Anyway
What is it?
Yeah, I was right. I see pretty outrageous stuff. I don't I don't know
Three funny
Basically just hitting on you guys
Hello miss our sir
What sir you don't want to put it in my hair
Need to tap I will leave it down
So, but yeah, it's not the story of, I keep talking about stories I don't want to see here, I'm sorry, but I will put up my Father's Psyche video, find it, and see what I made after Peter's biscuits, or just Peter's biscuits.
Here's a raw wild anthem, draft for
Then fades, he's done
I have too many things open obviously, okay, that's a cold society, okay, okay, so
I don't see, I don't see, I mean, I don't even see a bit, oh, oh, here's this one
No, that is a song, a beat that said she wrote for me, and then I found out the next day
She lied. It was actually written for some ex husband or boyfriend or something
Why would you tell me?
And then deny it the next day we have the video proof
Roll the tape
I like the panel-verse one that I made, but it's like the A, I thought, the thing,
panda-verse, and so it has all these pandas on computers and stuff, which is kind of cute,
though, still, but not really that good.
Got a keyboard army, but no paycheck yet
Sending pizza scrap man
Yeah it's from Timo. Is this thing wrong with that? I mean yeah my head is burning like there's
some chemical seeping into it but other than that is there a problem with the Timo wig? It's
actually even not in bad quality. Better than the parties. Okay there's actually a Timo wig
in there. There are like a couple steps above a party store. I'm not getting D.D. back his hair.
hair fair and square
Mirror cracked cards on the floor, who's who you asked?
I'm not sure anymore
You called me devil
What the fuck
Trips the fool, wears the crown
No moral here, no clean divide
We're just reflections that switch sides
Music is so long, you don't like it, babe?
People come here to these shoots to listen to people talk?
Well, no one's come on panel yet,
It's 4 in the fucking morning and I'm feeling like sharing new songs with me, so if you don't like it, kick rocks.
Bae.
Psyche walks with a ghost like a joke every face a mask every word a spell every promise
spun in the web of Jezebel bandits whisper blessings thieves wear crowns the prophets lost
the maps to these haunted towns he's been bound by silk by sin by code but his spirit still burns
In the way of Jezebel, he almost disappears
But the panther comes, all teeth and tears
Shadow
But the panther rose and the spell decays
Through the maze of mirrors, through smoke and fire
He walks out laughing untouched by the pyre
He's seen the fangs, the gilded deceit
But truth is a rhythm that won't concede
The soul don't fall, it just ascends
The web dissolves
The story bends
They can't kill what they don't know
In the web of Jezebel
I do have, like, a presentation coming up, like, soon.
I haven't, let's say, just have to do this.
But it's called The Web of Jezebel.
I wish I could find that.
I know where it is, kind of, oh my gosh,
there's this guy that explains it so well.
It's like, I should probably be doing it, but I don't really,
but it's like, yeah, we can find it today about it.
I mean, I can,
Talk a lot about it because there's a million parts to it. It's like it's a web, right?
So they have a million like little parts to it, but that's why
My brain transplants to a spider web
I mean so just a bill is kind of like right a lot of these figures are like
redeemed, right? Like even like Elizabeth Bathory, right? Who's like a mass murderer?
Vampire lady was actually redeemed.
You know, modern now they're saying, oh, she was just like, you know, doing medicine and like, you know,
experimenting on surgery, so I mean it's a little bit hard-pitched.
But you don't see it in the Bible. It was a quite a quite a wicked queen
She's been a shocking hand, right
Does it bother queen of things spirit fire? Well
Definitely the spirit
You could find a little short something about it
I'm gonna do some bibles Monday Monday. That's perfect for Bible study. It's actually interesting
Oh, it's we're gonna do that later. Oh
Oh my god, someone with question marks around their thing
What does it say? Hold on. Let me put my thing down.
Hello, yellow. Hi. How you been doing my guy?
All right
I've enjoyed your live in a minute, you know take some time off to see how you could do and you know
I swear to God yo you look like um something mouth boy from Harry Potter
Well, I was hoping I was like Pamela Anderson, but thanks anyway. No because you know why I've been playing the game and I watched a movie last night
I don't know. I'm just yeah, you're right about that generation
Like I was like a little bit like too old to enjoy Harry Potter like it's like, you know, I think it's like but um
Probably like 18 or like, you know
Listen never never never lose you any kid you heard when you lose that person you old
Yeah, I don't feel like I lost my inner kid. It's just like it's something I didn't read it as a child
And so I don't have that child of connection to it that a lot of things
I think that's an important part of like that wasn't your error. That wasn't more your error
They don't got to be your area if you like stuff like that like I like that mythical shit, so yeah
That's how I got into it. I got into it because of the mythical creatures in all that bullshit
I mean I read about you know people read the door of the ring and stuff for like years
Because you've definitely got the very pretty boy literature
of your life.
I don't like that fucking, who doesn't like to help King.
But yeah, I've been dropping in here and there,
psyche watching in, watching little techs here and there,
watching how it goes.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, here it goes.
Hey, Sam, how it goes, though?
There's ghosts right there, hi ghosts.
Oh shit, oh yeah, remember I told you that?
That's the same pitch. I got that picture from and they was like
Oh my god
I was like that looks just like him. I was like a little bit told you I told y'all that's the same pitch
I I screenshot it and I would make it fun. You see this picture. What do you think of this one?
That's you and who?
Who do you think? Oh?
Cool
Wow. Oh my gosh. Are people afraid of people? That's kind of scary.
No, I'm not afraid of her. I respect both of y'all. I'm not going to talk shit. Neither one of y'all.
I like both of y'all.
Good. I'm not asking you to talk shit. Oh my gosh. But like all of a sudden, people slam up over and they're going to say,
it's so funny. Whenever my name comes up.
No, I look because I'm rolling up right now.
What?
I'm rolling up right now. So when I look, I'm like, who the hell is that? Oh.
Wow
There's some you know some kind of like respect like more respect toward her than me like oh, no, dude
I
Actually don't go to either one you haven't been to either one of you since I've been arguing a lot
Like I haven't been to either one of you and I've been trying to stay away from the drama and shit
I'm trying to stay with away from ya drama like you know
I know this is why because I want to join and I I try to burn her the other day and say hi
Hey, I guess she was in her zone. She didn't probably see me in there or whatever so I left after like two minutes
I leave and then well
Yeah, I think it was packed that night too, so she wasn't part of the tension
Yeah, I support both of you guys, I'm just trying to stay out of the drama because I don't want to lose my mind right now, I'm just saying.
She's like she wrote some romantic like poem or something
You know really like sweet poem and then she said it was like for me when in tears crying
She said I just felt so bad. Oh my god, and then the next day. She's like why do you think I was in love with you?
I was like well, I didn't think that because I know it was probably just something to embarrass me in the end
but I was
But anyway, someone who's back in stage, let me see.
See, I haven't been on neither one of your pages.
I jumped on you guys' pages, like, I'll jump in,
and I'll see how I hit the like, and all that,
and just keep moving.
Arthur, it's time for you to talk shit.
Arthur, are you defending me in that way?
Oh, Arthur.
Arthur, do you think of some, like,
passive aggressive, like, stuff?
Like, I always go in there, and it's like,
are they talking about me?
And it's like, because it's like, sometimes they'll, like,
reference, like, things that they'll say psycho,
or those they'll say, like,
They'll kind of like emphasize it. I don't know if I'm just being paranoid, but it's like and then I think and then you're like
Are you like so you're like stop talking about psyche or something because there was like they're like referencing like some kind of insight
Yeah, they're always like about like it's like
You know the joke is it's like it doesn't seem like it's funny that what were they talking about they were talking about like
They're always like
This is their latest thing they're like that guy over there, you know the guy that thinks he could read tarry cards
But real quick real quick easy your little scumbag, huh?
About you and I've seen about you, huh about what what I do?
I've seen everything now
You know
What I did now
People you stabbing people when there's a legit fight
Man, I hope you go to prison, bro. I can't wait to you know
Take you've seen the video of this guy in a fight
Well, I'm gonna send you the video right now brother. Give me one second
So he he meets up with another youtuber right and he's talking hella shit
He's like yo like I can't believe you didn't want to collab with me
I've had it
You know I want to meet up and I want to fight with you he meets up with the other youtuber, right?
And so the other youtuber is like alright, dude. You've been talking hella shit. Let's do it
Let's do it the other youtuber literally knocks knocks him down to the ground and the youtuber feels bad for him
Right, so he's like you know what whatever that's it
And then guess what this dude easy goes into his pocket and shanks him bro. He starts to shank him like four or five times
Bro, that's that thing is crazy. I gotta send you the link. Can you can you?
Can I send you the video can you play?
I don't think I can play. I just don't want to play.
It's not, it's not gruesome.
It's not gruesome.
It's like, you know, I've seen it and it's like,
if people can look on their own, I don't want to play it on my show.
It's not gruesome though. It's not gruesome.
It's not gruesome. I've seen someone say,
I was sad and it's like, I have a chromatic
stuff about being people sad.
I can't. It's really hard, really.
Yeah, but this...
It's also like in my chat.
You're a mod. You can post something in the chat
and then everyone can check it out if they...
It's because, you know, maybe some content, you know, you could review something exposed a little
I don't want to air that, and that's like, and it's like, I hope it's easy for you to be like,
oh my god, is it, you know what, it's like, uh, out there already, and I don't, I'm not putting it
on my show, but, you know, it's like, but I'm sorry, I'm easy, if it's like, you know.
Man, you got exposed this little weasel. I can't wait till the feds get to him, bro
I hope he gets locked up for like at least minimum four or five years, bro. He's a little weasel. I
Mean, it's like this is not the safest show to go to if you're like, you know
Kind of hi
Okay
I think maybe I'm gonna play like a lot of going
It's already breaking you
There's the 20 people you had any time not speaking
Okay, well the link is up there. I don't know I think it's uncomfortable like
You know
with it and done so much.
My realm's unaffected, there's a door
Through the screen I spoke it real and it became
There's a dream inside the machine
I'll wake up deeper when I sleep
You'll understand when I delete
I went to God just to see
And the service showed me me
Heaven and hell were binary lies
When I ascend, your ego dies
And when you fail, my power
Get smaller, scar scar
Can you feel my power?
One spark and your truth gets darker
Let's bleed
Even in hell where empty dries, when I'm caught no flesh or vies
CAR!
with my screens when I'm light, the dark red team
You don't have to, you don't have to,
you don't have to keep divining yourself.
I mean, easy.
Like, whatever you want to, like, handle it.
But it's like, you know,
unfortunately, that's part of, like,
it's community is like,
they're really annoying.
Really annoying.
They don't shut up about things.
Like, I don't know.
But,
you know,
but,
you know, being,
people with that,
that thing.
Yeah, they're not happy, too.
They, they, they, they, they make homeless people.
And they, but they're talking about it.
I don't understand if some of the things that go on in some of these communities would be bad.
I am new. I'm new. And then everyone's like, oh my gosh, I should know everything.
Probably making out the best career choices. It's not like...
I mean, for a new look, this is a strange look, I think.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it should just be like Halloween,
and if I can probably be wearing this wig all the time.
I can already tell, I like love it.
Not, I think I'm getting high on the chemicals,
like, that are like, I can feel them like reaching into my skin.
The front itchy, but it's just hot,
it's kind of burning in a good way.
Anyway, it's almost 6 a.m.
People to go.
Okay, so.
You know, I'll just play my own video.
Right now, I won't get...
I've played so many copyright stuff, like all that carry-over piece that I've played that was nice.
It's like I got...
I mean, luckily...
You know, they aren't the big strengths for that, but we'll start great, right?
Crossroads even now
Your name burns behind my eyes
Three full goddess, mother of disguise
Through obsidian rain I need
That looks pretty, huh?
Let's see.
The shadows signed a name, a seal of frost upon the skin of time
Where death himself left a love note, pressed in the wax of tears
Like a grieving god, it's windows, cataracts of moonlight
It's all swollen with whispers of undone vows
If I could've stood beside a crib that night
I'd have held her through the rod and ruined
Kissed a ghost, still warm
In her veins, the moon ran blue
And in her silence, the stars
She was already gone Folded into legend
Into the marrow of the moon
Now she speaks and static through the ether
A signal from beyond the screen
My beauty is forgotten yet eternal
And when the black-eyed twins return
I've been missing in my sleep